(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
おめかし中...
Getting dressed...
イエーイ！みんなこんねねーー！！
Yay! Everyone, Konnene!!
というわけで、3月2日お誕生日があるの、桃鈴ねねでーす！
So, I'm Momosuzu Nene, whose birthday is on March 2nd!
イエーイ！みんな、お誕生日迎えました！みんなありがとう！
Yay! I've reached my birthday! Thank you, everyone!
今日はハッシュタグ、#桃鈴ねね誕生日2022 でたくさん呟いてください！みんな、あー見たい！トレンド入りしたところが見たいなー！
Please tweet a lot today with the hashtag #MomosuzuNeneBirthday2022! I want to see us trending!
というわけでたくさんツイートお願いしまーす！
So please, send out lots of tweets!
今日はですね、二部構成で行っていきたいと思います！
Today's show will be in two parts!
第一部がですね、えー、ゲストさんをお呼びして、もう収録が終了していますので、そこをみんなで見ていきたいと思います！
For the first part, we've invited some guests; it's already been recorded, so let's watch it together!
そして第二部は、あの、MCのゲストの人をお呼びして、生のソロパートを行っていきたいと思いますので、よかったら一時間お付き合いいただけると嬉しいです！
And for the second part, I'll have an MC guest and perform my solo part live, so I'd be happy if you'd stay with me for the hour!
というわけで、みんなステージ見て、ステージ！じゃーん、見て！うおー、すごい！
Anyway, look at the stage, everyone! Ta-da! Look! Whoa, it's amazing!
今回ね、ねねのお誕生日のために、スタジョスタッフさんたちがね、ちょっとねね仕様にアレンジしたステージを作ってくれました！
For my birthday, the studio staff created this stage arranged specifically for me!
イエーイ！あーみんなコメントいっぱいありがとう！
Yay! Thank you for all the comments, everyone!
というわけで早速ですね、まずはゲストパートを一緒に見ていきたいと思いますので、ねっこのみんな、今ねねの手にいるんだけど...
Without further ado, let's watch the guest part together. All you Nekkos are currently in my hands...
客席映んないとさゲストパート見れないからさ、みんなのこと客席にぶん投げていきたいと思います！
But you won't be able to see the guest part if the audience isn't shown, so I'm going to toss you all into the seats!
それではゲストパート行ってみよう！みんな行ってこーい！
Now then, let's get to the guest part! Off you go, everyone!
始まるよー！
It's starting!
めーるめるめる めるめるめるめ～ めーるめるめる めるめるめるめ～
Mel-meru-meru, meru-meru-meru-me~ Mel-meru-meru, meru-meru-meru-me~
宇宙にきらめく 流れ星☆
A shooting star sparkling in the universe☆
じーかーるじぇ～っとで、てーきを撃つ
With a magical jet, I shoot the enemy
魔法のくにから 地球のために
From a magical land, for the sake of Earth
落ちて 流れて こーんにちは
Falling, flowing, hello!
星くずうぃっちメルル～♪
Stardust Witch Meruru~♪
しゅーてぃんぐすた♪ しゅーてぃんぐすた♪
Shooting star♪ Shooting star♪
あなたの胸に飛び込んで行くの
I'm jumping into your heart
いん石よりも キラッ☆
More sparkling than a meteorite☆
きょだいなぱわーで
With a giant power
キラリッ☆
Sparkle☆
あなたのハートをねらい撃つの
I'll aim and shoot your heart
だ・か・ら よわたしの全力♪全開魔法♪
That's why! My full power! Full-throttle magic♪
逃げずに ちゃんと受け止めてよね〜
Don't run away, make sure to catch it properly~
めーるめるめる
Meru-meru-meru
めるめるめるめるめ〜
meru-meru-meru-meru-me~
虚空を舞い飛ぶ 女の子☆
A girl dancing and flying through the void☆
まじーかーる るっどで ほしを撃つ
Shooting stars with a magical rod
日本のすみから 宇宙のために
From a corner of Japan, for the sake of the universe
跳ねて 暴れて
Bounce, run wild,
ごーんにちわー
and helloooooo
星屑うぃっちメルル〜♪
Stardust Witch Meruru~♪
しゅ〜てぃんぐすた〜♪
Shooting star~♪
あなたの胸に飛び込んで行くの
I'm diving into your chest
太陽よりも 熱いカラダで
With a body hotter than the sun
あなたのすべて焼き尽くすの
I'll burn everything of yours to ashes
だ・か・ら よわたしの全力♪全開魔法♪
That's why! My full power! Full-throttle magic♪
逃げずに ちゃんと受け止めてよね〜
Don't run away, make sure to catch it properly~
銀河の果てから流星に乗って 落ちて流れてアイタタタ！
Riding a shooting star from the edge of the galaxy, falling and drifting, ouch ouch ouch!
みんな お待たせ！
Everyone, thanks for waiting!
ねねちと夜空メルでお送りしまーす！
Nenechi and Yozora Mel are bringing this to you!
星屑うぃっちメルル 行っきまーす！
Stardust Witch Meruru, here we go!
しゅ〜てぃんぐすた〜♪
Shooting star~♪
あなたの胸に飛び込んで行くの
I'm diving into your chest
流星よりも 強い気持ちで
With feelings stronger than a meteor
あなたのココロ抱きしめるの
I'll hold your heart tight
だ・か・ら よわたしの全力♪全開魔法♪
That's why! My full power! Full-throttle magic♪
逃げずに ちゃんと受け止めてよね〜
Don't run away, make sure to catch it properly~
めーるめるめる めるめるめるめ〜
Meru-meru-meru, meru-meru-meru-me~
名前のない怪物
Monster Without a Name
作詞・作曲：ryo(supercell)
Lyrics/Composition: ryo(supercell)
御伽話は さっき死んだみたい
It seems the fairy tale died just a moment ago
煉瓦の病棟で うまく歌えなくて
In the brick ward, I couldn't sing well
霧に 煙る夜
In the night hazy with fog
浮かべ 赤い月
A red moon floats
ほらみて 私を
Look at me
目を逸らさないで
Don't look away
黒い鉄格子のなかで 私は生まれてきたんだ
I was born within black iron bars
悪意の代償を望むがままに おまえに おまえに
Providing the price of malice as desired to you, to you
さあ与えよう
Now let's bestow
正義を 壊して
justice, destroying it
壊される前に 因果の代償を払い
Before being destroyed, pay the price of karma
共に行こう 名前のない怪物
Let's go together, monster without a name
耳鳴りがしてる 鉄条網うるさくて
My ears are ringing, the barbed wire is noisy
思い出せないの あの日の旋律
I can't remember the melody of that day
雨はまだ止まない
The rain hasn't stopped yet
何にも見えないの
I can't see anything
ほらみて こんなに
Look, see, like this
大きくなったの
It's grown so big
黒い雨 降らせこの空
Make the black rain fall from this sky
私は 望まれないもの
I am something unwanted
ひび割れた ノイローゼ 愛して
Love the cracked neurosis
同罪の 傍観者達に
To the accomplices, the bystanders
さあ今 震え 正義を
Now, tremble, justice
消せない 傷を抱きしめて
Embrace the wounds that can't be erased
この体を 受け入れ
Accept this body
共に行こう 名前のない
Let's go together, the monster
怪物
without a name
ああ ああ
Ah, ah
神は
God
告げる
proclaims
神ハ告ゲル
God proclaims
真ノ
The true
世界ヲ
world
鉄格子 の中で
Inside the iron bars
私は 生まれてきたんだ
I was born
悪意の 代償を 望むがままに
As you wish, the price of malice
お前に お前に お前に
To you, to you, to you
さあ与えよう 正義を 壊して
Now, I'll give you justice, destroy it
壊される 前に
Before it is destroyed
因果の 代償を 払い報いよ
Pay the price of karma, meet your fate
名もなき怪物
Nameless monster
黒い雨 降らせこの空
Make the black rain fall from this sky
私は 望まれないもの
I am something unwanted
ひび割れた ノイローゼ 愛して
Love the cracked neurosis
同罪の 傍観者達に
To the accomplices, the bystanders
さあ今 震え 正義を
Now, tremble, justice
消せない 傷を抱きしめて
Embrace the wounds that can't be erased
この体を 受け入れ
Accept this body
共に行こう 名前のない
Let's go together, the monster
怪物
without a name
名前のない怪物をお聞きいただきました！ありがとうございました！
You just heard 'Monster Without a Name'! Thank you very much!
ダースビ！ ダースビ！
Dasubi! Dasubi!
えっと、ダクスタピッツね？
Um, it's Dakustapittsu, right?
そう、ダクスタピッツ。
Yes, Dakustapittsu.
もう略して一生。
Let's just abbreviate it forever.
正式名称 NG。
Official name is NG.
NG。おぉ。
NG. Oh.
ということで、ねねね、お誕生日おめでとう！
And so, Nene-ne, happy birthday!
やったー！ありがとうございます！
Yay! Thank you very much!
二人とも来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you both for coming!
いや、今回もね、ダンス頑張りましたね。
Man, we really worked hard on the dancing this time too.
頑張った。
We did.
今回、練習期間がすっごく短かった！
The practice period was so short this time!
短かった！
It was short!
でも、やっぱりみんなダンス覚えるのが早い！
But as expected, everyone learns dances so fast!
早い、みんなすごい。
Fast, everyone's amazing.
本当、一瞬だったよ。頑張った。
It was really in an instant. We worked hard.
家でめっちゃやってきたんだなって。
I could tell you did a lot of practice at home.
それはもう、めっちゃやった。
Of course, I did a ton.
ここで？
Here?
これね？
This part?
これ、これめっちゃ難しい。
This, this part is really hard.
もうみんなで、え、え、え、え。
Everyone was like, 'Eh? Eh? Eh? Eh?'
むずいんだよな、このステップね。
This step is hard, isn't it?
なんか、先生がさ、軽々やるからできるかなって思ったらできないんだよね。
The teacher does it so easily so I thought I could do it, but I couldn't.
そう、できないんだよね。
Yeah, you can't.
でも、できるようになったよね、みんな。
But we learned how to do it, didn't we?
なってた、なってた。
We did, we did.
私はね、ここが。
For me, this part...
そうそう、この移動がね、難しい。
Right, this movement is hard.
できてたね、みんなね。
Everyone was doing it well.
超かっこよかったと思う。
I think it looked super cool.
かっこよかったよね。
It was cool, right?
エモい。
Emo.
エモい、エモい。
Emo, emo.
エモ、エモ。
いやあ、疲れちゃって。
Man, I'm tired out.
疲れちゃった。
Tired out.
これ大変だったよ、やっぱり。
It was tough, after all.
大変だった。
It was tough.
でもね、でもね、ねねはね、今からもちょっとまだ。
But you know, Nene still has a little bit more from now.
あ、そうだ。
Ah, that's right.
続くわ。
It continues.
そうだね。
That's right.
でもね、二人とまた踊れて本当に嬉しかった。ありがとう。
But you know, I was really happy to be able to dance with you two again. Thank you.
また踊る。
Let's dance again.
また踊ろう！
Let's dance again!
あ、ダッピ...
Ah, Dappi...
ダッピよろしくお願いします！
We are Dappi, nice to meet you!
イェーイ！
Yay!
え、次、待って、ちょっと次の話をするとさ...
Wait, if we talk about what's next...
次はどんな感じの踊りたい？歌いたい？
What kind of song do you want to sing and dance to next?
えー、三人で？
Hmm, the three of us?
なんか、うーん...
Like, hmm...
K-POPみたいなやつやりたい。
I want to do something like K-POP.
あー！
Ah!
でもそれもやっぱりダンスまた激しいやつよ。
But that would involve some intense dancing again.
激しいやつよ。
Yeah, intense.
めっちゃ難しいじゃん。
That sounds really hard.
ズンズクズンズクズンズクズンみたいなやつ。
Something with a beat like "zun-zuku-zun-zuku".
ズン...
Zun...
カニ歩きとかありそうだけど。
It might even have a crab walk.
あー、ありそう。
Oh, probably.
やだー！
No way!
え、ありそうでしょ？
Come on, it's possible, right?
あるかもしれない。
Maybe so.
あるかも。
Maybe.
やりたいね、またね。
I'd love to do it again sometime.
やりたいねー！
Me too!
お楽しみに！
Look forward to it!
また次のダッピをお楽しみに！
Please look forward to Dappi's next performance!
お楽しみにー！
Look forward to it!
イェーイ！
Yay!
もう朝も昼も今日も明日もくじけない！
Morning, noon, today, and tomorrow, I won't give up!
うおーーーーーー！
Whoa!
つまりはいつもくじけない！
Anyway, I'll never give up!
あぁ…… 今日も失敗したらしい うまくいかない
Ah... I failed again today, things aren't going well.
凹んだけれど悔いなし！ そんな日もあるよ
I'm feeling down but no regrets! Days like this happen.
結構ある…… 結構ある……
It happens quite often... Quite often...
半泣きだけどハッピーです！
I'm almost in tears but I'm happy!
虎視眈々狙い撃ち
Vigilantly watching for a chance to strike.
めちゃでかい野望持ってます
I have a massive ambition.
人生なんてほらほらね
You see, life is...
谷あり谷あり…… なんで？
...full of ups and downs... Wait, why?
前だけを見て進め
Just look forward and move ahead.
どっちが前だ！？
Which way is forward!?
無限算 つまりくじけない
Infinite calculations, meaning I won't give up.
今日がダメでも明日は Just-hit
Even if today is bad, tomorrow will be a just-hit.
傷心からの一步前進
One step forward from a broken heart.
そんでもって今、変身
And so, right now, I'm transforming.
もっとポジティブ いつもくじけない
Be more positive, I'll never give up.
「あきらめ」なんて辞書にない
The word 'giving up' isn't in my dictionary.
前途多難なんだか 壁はちょっと高いけど
The future looks difficult, and the wall is a bit high, but...
もう朝も昼も今日も明日もくじけない！
Morning, noon, today, and tomorrow, I won't give up!
うおーーーーーー！
Whoa!
また一步進み一步戻る
One step forward and one step back again.
せつないけれどくじけない
It's painful, but I won't give up.
強がりモードは解けないけど
I can't turn off my 'act tough' mode, but...
ゴメンはちゃんと 言えますです……
I can say 'I'm sorry' properly...
結果ぜんぜん出ない日々
Days when I get no results at all.
それも全部計算のうち（？）
That's all part of the plan (?)
ぐーぐーお腹が減った
My stomach is growling.
飯テロめ…… 今に見てろ……
Damn food porn... Just you wait...
食べ放題 酒池肉林
All-you-can-eat, a feast of food and drink.
もーすぐきっと……！
Very soon, for sure...!
Never give up つまりくじけない
Never give up, meaning I won't give up.
今日があるから明日がある
There's a tomorrow because there's a today.
1000回無理？ じゃ1001回
1000 times impossible? Then make it 1001 times.
限界なんてない！
There are no limits!
せーのでもっと いつもくじけない
Altogether now, I'll never give up.
後悔ばっかしちゃうけど
I often end up having regrets, but...
全身全霊かけて 毎日を生きてます！
I'm living every day with all my heart and soul!
泣いてる？ 泣いてない！ くじけた？
Are you crying? No! Did you give up?
全然くじけてないです
I haven't given up at all.
不幸自慢 飛んでけ
Away with your tales of woe.
もう どこか遠く捉えよう
Let's capture it somewhere far away.
さあ夢を叶えよう
Come on, let's make our dreams come true.
夢は叶うよ ハイ！ 夢は叶うよ ハイ！
Dreams come true! Yes! Dreams come true! Yes!
準備は完了
Preparations complete.
急げ急げ急げ急げ急げ急げ Go Go!
Hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry! Go Go!
無限算 つまりくじけない
Infinite calculations, meaning I won't give up.
今日がダメでも明日は Just-hit
Even if today is bad, tomorrow will be a just-hit.
傷心からの一步前進
One step forward from a broken heart.
そんでもって今、変身
And so, right now, I'm transforming.
もっとポジティブ いつもくじけない
Be more positive, I'll never give up.
「あきらめ」なんて辞書にない
The word 'giving up' isn't in my dictionary.
前途多難なんだか 壁はちょっと高いけど
The future looks difficult, and the wall is a bit high, but...
もう朝も昼も今日も明日も永遠に
Morning, noon, today, and tomorrow, forever.
つまりなんかええとそうだくじけない！
Anyway, uh, yeah, I won't give up!
うおーーーーーー！
Whoa!
手を上げて
Put your hands up.
Clap your hands 海の向こうまで
Clap your hands, across the sea.
Clap your hands 届きますように
Clap your hands, so it reaches you.
手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands.
ほら一緒に
Come on, everyone together.
Everybody
Clap your hands 空の向こうまで
Clap your hands, to the other side of the sky.
Clap your hands 響きますように
Clap your hands, so it resonates.
手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands.
光射す 僕たちの未来
A light shines on our future.
FIVE
FOUR
THREE
TWO
ONE
hololive 5th Stars
始めようか　さあ Diving
Let's begin, now diving
待っても意味ない タイミング
There's no point in waiting for the right timing
あの魚みたいに Swimming Swimming
Like that fish, swimming swimming
引き寄せるの Lighting
Drawing it in, lighting
まだ見えないよ Maybe
I still can't see it, maybe
この先には何があるの？
What lies ahead?
まだ早いよ Take it
It's still too early, take it
追いつくまで Shaking
Until I catch up, shaking
でもたまに止まって Thinking Thinking
But sometimes I stop, thinking thinking
変えてみせる Change
I'll show you I can change
踏み出すのさ Stepping
Taking the first step, stepping
掴んでみせるよ　キラキラ My Dream
I'll seize it, my sparkling dream
叶う日まで Story つなぐから
Until it comes true, I'll keep connecting the story
だって君にずっと見てほしいから
Because I want you to keep watching me
手を叩こう　Clap your hands
Let's clap our hands, clap your hands
海の向こうまで
All the way across the sea
手を叩こう　Clap your hands
Let's clap our hands, clap your hands
届きますように
So that it reaches you
手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands
ほら一緒に Everybody
Come on, together everybody
手を叩こう　Clap your hands
Let's clap our hands, clap your hands
空の向こうまで
All the way across the sky
手を叩こう　Clap your hands
Let's clap our hands, clap your hands
響きますように
So that it resonates
手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands
光射す
The light shines
僕たちの未来
Upon our future
今日は要らない　ブレーキ
No need for brakes today
理性壊せ Breaking
Break down your reason, breaking
何時でもいいでしょ？　四六時中
Any time is fine, right? All day and night
君は何を Feeling?
What are you feeling?
解き放て Sparking
Let it loose, sparking
暗闇に放つ　レーザービーム
Shoot a laser beam into the darkness
光らせて Stage 作るから
I'll make the stage shine
だって君にもっと見てほしいから
Because I want you to see more
手を叩こう　Clap your hands
Let's clap our hands, clap your hands
海の向こうまで
All the way across the sea
手を叩こう　Clap your hands
Let's clap our hands, clap your hands
届きますように
So that it reaches you
手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands
ほら一緒に Everybody
Come on, together everybody
手を叩こう　Clap your hands
Let's clap our hands, clap your hands
空の向こうまで
All the way across the sky
手を叩こう　Clap your hands
Let's clap our hands, clap your hands
響きますように
So that it resonates
手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands
重なる声
Uniting voices
世界を揺らせ
Shake the world
終わりがあることくらい　既に I know
I already know that there's an end
でもまだまだ泳ぎ足りないの
But I still haven't swum enough
Give me crazy
まるで Lazy
Just like lazy
BOOM!!!!
次元混ざり合うの　全て塗り替える BLUE
Dimensions merging, repainting everything BLUE
手を叩こう　Clap your hands
Let's clap our hands, clap your hands
海の向こうまで
All the way across the sea
手を叩こう　Clap your hands
Let's clap our hands, clap your hands
届きますように
So that it reaches you
手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands
ほら一緒に Everybody
Come on, together everybody
手を叩こう　Clap your hands
Let's clap our hands, clap your hands
空の向こうまで
All the way across the sky
手を叩こう　Clap your hands
Let's clap our hands, clap your hands
響きますように
So that it resonates
手を叩こう
Let's clap our hands
光射す
The light shines
僕たちの未来
Upon our future
はーい！ということでいかがでしたでしょうか、ゲストパート！
Hi! So, how was the guest part?
皆さん改めてお祝いしてくれてありがとうございます！
Thank you everyone once again for celebrating with me!
先輩たちみんな来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you all the seniors for coming!
そしてですね、ここからはですね、生でお届けしていきたいと思っているのですが...
And from here, I'd like to bring it to you live...
なんと先程ね、初めてのね、4人でのブルクラやったりして、ブルクラ歌ったんで、ね、ポルボラの皆に来てもらってまーす！
And just now, for the first time, the four of us performed BLUE CLAPPER together! Since we sang BLUE CLAPPER, the PolBoRa members are here!
皆ね、お祝いしに来ちゃって...!
Everyone came to celebrate...!
せーの！
One, two!
Happy Birthday to you, Happy Birthday to you
Happy Birthday dear ねね, Happy Birthday to you
Happy Birthday dear Nene, Happy Birthday to you
ありがとう！
Thank you!
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
ありがとうみんな！
Thank you everyone!
ちょっとブルクラ、ブルクラどうだった？ちょっと聞くの早かったかな？
Hey, how was BLUE CLAPPER? Maybe it's a bit too soon to ask?
なんかもー余韻なんもねーなｗ
The afterglow is already gone lol
なんもねーよｗ
It's gone lol
いや、あの、すごいなと思って感動しちゃって。
No, I just thought it was amazing and got moved.
よかったです！あのね、久しぶりに思い出した。
It was great! You know, I remembered it for the first time in a while.
おおすごい！
Oh wow!
あの感覚、体が覚えているっていう...
That feeling, my body remembers...
おおすごい！
Oh wow!
さあ４人で練習したりとかな...
So, the four of us practiced together and all...
そうそう
Yeah, yeah.
今回初めて４人でやったんですけど...
We did it with the four of us for the first time...
ちょっとねね、お気に入りのとこがあって発表したい！
Nene has a favorite part she wants to announce!
どこどこどこ？
Where, where, where?
おまるのラップの...「悪いおまるがあることくらいすでにI know」
In Omaru's rap... "I already know there's a bad Omaru."
悪いおまるがいた
A bad Omaru was there.
私、悪くなります！
I'm gonna be bad!
悪くなるぞ！悪くなるぞ！
Gonna be bad! Gonna be bad!
悪くなるのに消沈する瞬間があるのね
There's a moment of dejection despite being 'bad.'
そこまでめっちゃ普通だったのに急に...
It was so normal until then, but suddenly...
「悪くなるぞ！」とか言って、めっちゃ悪かった！
She said "I'm gonna be bad!" and she was so bad!
あれホント好きでね...
I really loved that part...
ここをとかめっちゃ綺麗に揃ってホント良かった
This part synced up so perfectly, it was great.
練習したもんね、あそこね
We practiced that part, didn't we?
すごかった、すごかった
It was amazing, amazing.
びしばし、びしばし...
Bishibashi, bishibashi...
ここだけは合わせようってね
We said, "Let's at least get this part in sync."
でもようやく、だね、ホントに
But finally, we did it, really.
そうだね、そうだね。よかった、ありがとう！
That's right, that's right. I'm glad, thank you!
あのさ、次からさ、ねねのソロ曲が始まるんだけど...
Hey, after this, Nene's solo song is starting...
ほお？
Oh?
ちょっと次の一曲さ、絶対盛り上がる曲だからさ、みんなにここにいてほしいんだよねね
The next song is definitely gonna be a hit, so I want everyone to stay here.
途中退場...？
Leaving in the middle...?
え？ちょっと待って？なんで退場すること前提なの？
Eh? Wait? Why are you assuming you'll leave?
ちゃんといた曲だったら、ずっと「ああ...」って聞いてるんだけど...
If it were a proper song, we'd stay and listen, but...
ちょっとしてる！ソロステージなのよ！
I am doing one! It's a solo stage!
とってもいい曲ね、あの...
It's a very good song, um...
絶対にちょっと一人じゃ恥ずかしくてできない曲やるんだけど
I'm gonna do a song that's definitely too embarrassing to do alone.
恥ずかしいんか？
Is it embarrassing?
そこまで言われると帰りたくなってきた
Since you put it that way, I want to go home now.
だからみんな自由にしていいていいから、その代わりに
So you can all do whatever you want instead.
何してもいいの？
Anything's fine?
何してもいい。スマホ触ってもいい
Anything's fine. You can use your phones.
ツイッターしてもいい？
Can I use Twitter?
いいよ、ツイッターして
Sure, go ahead.
エゴサしとくわ
I'll do some ego-searching.
あいのてちゃんとやるんだろう？みんなあいのてやってね
You'll do the calls properly, right? Everyone, do the calls.
エゴサしとくわ、じゃあ
I'll do some ego-searching then.
誕生日タグでツイッター、エゴサして...
Twitter birthday tag, ego-search...
じゃあみんな各自、はい、じゃあ好きに...好きに...
Then everyone individually... okay, as you like...
ねねちょっとお水飲んでくるからさ
Nene's gonna go drink some water.
ゆっくり...ゆっくりさせてもらうね
We'll... take it easy then.
わあ、雑談する感じだね。イエーイ！
Wow, it's like a chat stream. Yay!
そっと...？
Quietly...?
おまるはあいのて、おまるもあいのてしてくれるって信じているよ
I believe Omaru will do the calls for me too.
あ、そうそう、いいえいいえ！
Ah, yes yes, good good!
あれ？二人...？
Huh? The two of you...?
どっかのライブかな？
Is this a concert somewhere?
なんてさ！ねねがお水飲みに行って...あれ？
Why! While Nene went to drink water... huh?
おい！出てすんな！誕生日だからエゴサするんだから！
Hey! Don't space out! I'm ego-searching because it's my birthday!
エゴサしてます
I'm ego-searching.
エゴサそれは...嗜みながら聴きます
Ego-searching... I'll listen while enjoying that.
わかった。じゃあちょっと心を込めて歌わせていただきます
Got it. Then I'll sing with all my heart.
よし！それでは聴いてください。「チチをもげ！」
Alright! Please listen. "Chichi wo Moge!"
え？変えていい？
Eh? Can I change it?
ダメだよ！帰るな！帰るのダメ！
No way! Don't go! Going home is no good!
みんなのチチもぐの！
I'm gonna pluck everyone's boobs!
やめてよ！
Stop it!
チッチッチッチ おっぱい
Chi-chi-chi-chi Boobs
ボインボイン
Boin boin!
チッチッチッチ おっぱい
Chi-chi-chi-chi Boobs
ボインボイン
Boin boin!
もげ もげもげもげ
Pluck, pluck-pluck-pluck
さあ合の手してね みんな 一緒に合の手してください
Now do the calls, everyone! Everyone, do the calls together!
今日は、ツイッター、みんな、ツイッター、みんなのチチをもぎたいと思います！
Today, Twitter, everyone, Twitter, I'm gonna pluck everyone's boobs!
もげ もげもげ チチをもげ！
Pluck, pluck-pluck, pluck the boobs!
もげたいボイン もげたいボイン
Wanna pluck 'em, boin boin
もーげ ポヨン
Pluck, poyon
もーげ ポロロン プヨン もげ
Pluck, poloron puyon pluck
まんまるチッチッ 三角おっぱい ロケットボイーン
Round boobs, triangular boobs, rocket boin!
優しく もげ
Pluck 'em gently
いきなり もげ
Pluck 'em suddenly
微妙に もげ
Pluck 'em subtly
連続 もげ
Pluck 'em repeatedly
もげもげもげもげ
Pluck-pluck-pluck-pluck
チッチッチッチ おっぱい せーの！
Chi-chi-chi-chi Boobs, ready, go!
ボインボイン
Boin boin!
チッチッチッチ おっぱい せーの！
Chi-chi-chi-chi Boobs, ready, go!
ボインボイン
Boin boin!
もげ もげもげもげ チチをもげ！ もげー！
Pluck, pluck-pluck-pluck, pluck the boobs! Pluck!
ナイス合の手ありがとうみんな！
Thanks for the nice calls, everyone!
次はししらみのチチを揉んでいきたいと思います！
Next, I'm gonna massage Shishirami's boobs!
日本酒ってなんなのよ！
What is up with this sake!
もげもげもげ チチをもげ！
Pluck-pluck-pluck, pluck the boobs!
もげポヨおっぱいもげー もげパイボインもげー
Pluck poyo boobs pluck, pluck pie boin pluck
しましまチッチッ おさるのおっぱい バズーカボイーン
Striped boobs, monkey boobs, bazooka boin!
今日も もげ
Pluck 'em today
明日も もげ
Pluck 'em tomorrow
とにかく もげ
Just pluck 'em
毎日 もげ
Pluck 'em every day
チッチッチッチ おっぱい せーの！
Chi-chi-chi-chi Boobs, ready, go!
ボインボイン
Boin boin!
チッチッチッチ おっぱい せーの！
Chi-chi-chi-chi Boobs, ready, go!
ボインボイン
Boin boin!
もげ もげもげもげ チチをもげ！ もげー！
Pluck, pluck-pluck-pluck, pluck the boobs! Pluck!
ははは 待て待て待て待て！ 捕まえて！
Hahaha, wait wait wait wait! Catch her!
お前らも歌ってあげてな！
You guys sing along too!
はい、もい一回！
Okay, one more time!
あー！いやん！そこは！
Ah! No! Not there!
ボインよー！
It's boing!
ちゃんとツイートしてくれたかな？
Did you guys tweet properly?
チッチッチッチおっぱい
Chi-chi-chi-chi boobies
ボインボイン
Boing boing
チッチッチッチおっぱい
Chi-chi-chi-chi boobies
せーの！
Ready, set...
ボインボイン
Boing boing
さあ、はい！
Come on!
チッチッチッチおっぱい
Chi-chi-chi-chi boobies
ボインボイン
Boing boing
チッチッチッチおっぱい
Chi-chi-chi-chi boobies
ボインボイン
Boing boing
もげもげもげ
Moge moge moge
乳母もげー！
Squeeze the boobies!
つかれた
I'm tired
もげ！もげ！
Moge! Moge!
乳母もげ！
Squeeze the boobies!
もげ！
Moge!
断末魔うるさ
Those death rattles are noisy.
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you very much!
いや、もう絶対やりたかったんだよ。
Man, I really wanted to do that.
3人ともお付き合いいただきまして、本当にありがとうございました。
Thank you three so much for joining me.
本当にやりたかったことこれなんだ。
This is what I truly wanted to do.
これなの？
This is it?
なんか、ブルクラより楽しそうだったみたい。
You looked like you were having more fun than in Blue Journey.
大丈夫？ねえ、ブルクラよりちょっと楽しそうだった。
Is that okay? You looked a bit more fun than in Blue Journey.
大丈夫だよ。ブルクラはやっぱ完成度が欲しかったけど。
It's fine. For Blue Journey, I wanted perfection.
これは、楽しんでやりたかったの。
But for this, I wanted to just have fun.
ある種の完成度はあったよ。あったあった。
There was a certain kind of perfection. Yeah, there was.
あ、園長の電話大丈夫？
Oh, is the director's phone call okay?
あ、大丈夫。園長、延長しといて。
Ah, it's fine. Director, please extend it.
延長する回路？
An extension circuit?
ちょっと、みんなに言うけど、これねねの生誕祭ライブ。
Wait, I'm telling everyone, this is Nene's birthday live.
カラオケじゃない。
Not karaoke.
本当はね、みんな。
The truth is, everyone...
カラオケじゃなかった。
It wasn't karaoke.
ここライブのステージで、みんな見てるの、今。
This is a live stage, and everyone's watching right now.
イェーイ！
Yay!
コメント見てるかー？
Are you guys looking at the comments?
楽しかったなー。
That was fun.
そうだよ、ライブですよ。
That's right, it's a live concert.
こっからね、まだあるんだけどね、こっからちょっと真剣パートだから。
There's more to come, but from here on, it's the serious part.
ちょっとみんな入って。
So everyone, please go inside.
これ何だったの？カラオケじゃねーかよ、やっぱり。
Then what was that? It was just karaoke after all.
恥ずかしいから、みんな入って！
It's embarrassing, so everyone, go inside!
わかったよ。バイバーイ！
Alright. Bye-bye!
もむ？
Squeeze?
みんな…いいよ、揉んでけ！
Everyone... fine, squeeze away!
見せないで。ちょっと。
Don't show them. Wait.
耳に入っちゃダメ！ダメダメ！
Not in the ear! No no!
バイバーイ！お疲れ！
Bye-bye! Good job!
ありがとありがと。
Thanks, thanks.
みんな休憩してもらって。
Everyone, please take a break.
次の曲に移らせていただきたいと思います。
I'd like to move on to the next song.
ここからね、もうねねの超超真剣アイドルモードをお聴きください。
From here, please listen to Nene's super-duper serious idol mode.
それでは次の曲いきたいと思います。
Well then, let's go to the next song.
Precious.
心が見えなくて
Because I couldn't see your heart
不安な日もあった
there were days when I felt anxious
誰かを愛する意味
The meaning of loving someone
自分なりに決めた
I decided in my own way
すべてを信じ抜くこと
To believe in everything until the end
I promise you
もう迷わない
I won't hesitate anymore
強くなる…
I will become strong...
あなたに託すよ
I'll entrust it to you
逃げないで 向き合っていく
Not running away, I'll face it
姿を見せてくれた
You showed me how to do it
to heart
信じよう
Let's believe
ふたりだから
Because it's the two of us
愛し合える
We can love each other
あの空へ
Toward that sky
願いが届くように
So that our wishes reach it
見つめあい
Gazing at each other
祈る to for us
Praying for us
ふたつ重ねた想いが今
Our two feelings joined together now
ひとつの形に変わる
change into a single shape
Your precious love
傷つき
Getting hurt
苦しむなら
if you are suffering...
分けあって
Sharing with each other
抱きしめ合おう
Let's hold each other
もうひとりじゃないから
Because you're not alone anymore
全てを受け止めるよ
I'll accept everything
true love
信じよう
Let's believe
ふたりだから
Because it's the two of us
愛しあえる
We can love each other
永遠につないだ
Joined for eternity
この手をもう離さない
I won't let go of this hand again
誓う two of us
I swear, the two of us
ふたつ重ねた想いが今
Our two layered feelings now
ひとつの形に変わる
Turn into a single shape
Just the two of us
間違えちゃいました、あはは
I messed up, ahaha
笑わせないで！
Stop making me laugh!
幼かったひとりよがりの愛
An immature, self-centered love
今は強く信じあえる
Now we can strongly believe in each other
There can be truth 新しい始まり
There can be truth, a new beginning
I want to be one with you
信じよう
Let's believe
ふたりは今
The two of us now
愛しあい
Loving each other
此処にいる
Being right here
光が満ちるように
So the light may overflow
抱きしめるあなたを
I'll hold you close
信じよう
Let's believe
ふたりだから
Because it's the two of us
愛しあえる
We can love each other
あの空へ願いが
Our wishes toward that sky
届くように
May they reach it
見つめあい
Gazing at each other
祈る two of us
Praying, the two of us
ふたつ重ねた想いが今
Our two layered feelings now
ひとつの形に変わる
Turn into a single shape
Your precious love
みんなありがとう！ちょっと間違えちゃってごめんね！
Thank you everyone! Sorry I messed up a little bit!
あと、おまる袖から見てるの知ってるんだからね！
Also, Omaru, I know you're watching from the wings!
笑わせようとしないで！踊ってたでしょ、さっき！
Don't try to make me laugh! You were dancing earlier, weren't you!
みんなありがとう！
Thank you everyone!
ゴンドラ見てみてくれ！
Look at the gondola!
実はね、根っこのみんなと一緒に
Actually, you see, I wanted to stand
ステージに立ちたくてゴンドラに根っこくっつけてもらったんだ！
on stage with all the Nekko, so I had them attached to the gondola!
どうかな？ありがとう！
How is it? Thank you!
みんなこれからも一緒にアイドルのステージをやっていこうね！
Let's continue to do idol stages together from now on, everyone!
この後ゴンドラから降りるので一旦暗くなります！
I'll be getting off the gondola after this, so it'll go dark for a moment!
はい！というわけで、Preciousをお聞きいただきました！ありがとうございました！
Yes! And so, you just heard 'Precious'! Thank you very much!
イェーイ！イェーイ！
Yeah! Yeah!
両脇にね、みんながいてくれてるんですよ、今。手振っちゃった。
Everyone is right here on both sides of me now. I waved.
あ、根っこだのね。ありがとう。
Ah, it's the Nekko. Thank you.
というわけで、なんとソロのパート次が、え、ラストの曲になるんですけど...
And so, believe it or not, the next song in the solo part is the last song...
はっ！Twitterのトレンド1位なんだって！
Hah! I heard we're #1 on Twitter trends!
みんなありがとう！呟いてくれてありがとね、みんな！
Thank you everyone! Thanks for tweeting, guys!
みんな衝撃受けちゃったかな？ねねの完成度の高い乳もげに。
Did everyone get shocked? By Nene's high-quality Chichimoge.
びっくりしたんだろうな、みんな。あはは。
Everyone must have been surprised. Ahaha.
カメラマンさんが、あはは！
The cameraman is, ahaha!
というわけで次にする曲ラストになってしまうんですけど、
So, the next song will be the last,
あのちょっとね、アンコールがもしかしたらあるかもしれないので、
but you see, there might just be an encore,
皆さん、あの、まだ「終わりだな」って思わないようにしてください。
everyone, so please don't think 'it's over' just yet.
もしかしたらだけど、アンコールあるかもしれないので。
Just maybe, there might be an encore.
というわけで、聞いてください。えー次の曲、最後の曲、次は...
So, please listen. The next song, the final song, next is...
ねねの、大好きな、大好きな、
Nene's beloved, beloved,
神田沙也加さんの曲から一曲歌わせていただきたいと思います。
I'd like to sing a song by Sayaka Kanda.
それでは聴いてください。
Please listen.
Break Beat Bark!
警報が響いて
The alarm sounds
包囲網でガンジガラメ
Trapped in the surrounding net
Checkmate寸前
On the verge of checkmate
Countdownが嫌らしいな
The countdown is so nasty
勝手な欲望で
By selfish desires
踏みつけられたって
Even if trampled upon
僕のセオリーじゃ
In my theory
答えは No! Are you kidding me?
The answer is No! Are you kidding me?
僕の刻んだメモリーを
The memories I've carved
君と作り上げてきたリアルを
The reality I've built with you
イレギュラーになんて奪わせるな
Don't let any irregularity take it away
Break Beat Bark!
まだ見えない
Not visible yet
未来って単純じゃない
The future isn't simple
ダンジョンみたい Can't see
It's like a dungeon, can't see
だけど Heads up!
But heads up!
すぐそこさ Never give up!
It's right there, never give up!
パスワードはそれで十分なんだ
That's enough for a password
君と僕の
Yours and mine
純粋すぎる理想
Our too-pure ideals
捨てられないね？ Happy
We can't throw them away, right? Happy
叫び出せ願いの限り
Shout out as much as you wish
冗談じゃないって言う間に
Before I can say it's no joke
足を奪われ K.O.偽装で
Tripped up, in a faked K.O.
“YOU LOSE...” ふざけてる！
'YOU LOSE...' You're kidding!
正々堂々を逃げたって
Even if you run from fair play
僕はここさ
I'm right here
もう手遅れだね Yes, you are kidding me!
It's too late now, yes, you are kidding me!
守るべきはずの約束を
The promise that should have been kept
その中で育ててきた希望を
The hope nurtured within it
バイオレートさせちゃいけないんだ
We must not let it violate
Break Beat Bark!
遠ざかって
Receding
明日へルートがまた
The route to tomorrow again
ループみたく Long way round
Like a loop, a long way round
だけど Wake up!
But wake up!
朝が来て Hello, my hope!
Morning comes, hello, my hope!
変換不能な意志があれば
If there's an unconvertible will
君と僕で立ち向かう壁
The wall we face together
熱くなるでしょ？ Happy
It's getting hot, right? Happy
叫び出す祈りを込めて
Shouting out, putting our prayers into it
涙の落ちる音がした
I heard the sound of tears falling
今も耳に響いてる
It's still echoing in my ears
音の速さで助けに行くよ
I'll go to save you at the speed of sound
強くなれ この振動
Become stronger, this vibration
誰かを救うため戦い抜くために
To save someone, to fight to the end
Break Beat Bark!
見えてきた
I can see it now
未来って単純じゃない
The future isn't simple
ダンジョンじゃない Let's see
It's not a dungeon, let's see
そうさ Heads up!
That's right, heads up!
すぐそこさ Never give up!
It's right there, never give up!
パスワードはもう必要ないんだ
A password is no longer needed
君と僕の
Yours and mine
純粋すぎる理想
Our too-pure ideals
叶えなきゃないね？ Happy
We have to make them come true, right? Happy
叫び出せ願いの限り
Shout out as much as you wish
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you so much!
みんな、またねねー！かもしれない、かもしれない、かもしれないー
Everyone, see you again-nene! Maybe, maybe, maybe~
アンコール！アンコール！
Encore! Encore!
アンコール！ アンコール！
アンコールありがとうー！
Thank you for the encore!
揺れすぎるぞ、やめとこｗ
It's shaking too much, I'll stop lol
というわけで、初お披露目、ねねの通常衣装の上着の衣装になります！
So, for the first time, this is Nene's regular outfit's jacket!
このまま、最後の、本当の本当の最後の1曲聞いてください。
Now, please listen to the last, the very, very last song.
ebb and flow。
ebb and flow.
降り積もる粉雪が舞う
Falling, piling powdered snow dances
諦めかけた夢がまだ
The dream I almost gave up on still...
波打つあの日のままで
Is rippling, just like that day
変わらない笑顔見つめた
I gazed at that unchanging smile
染まる頬に触れた風が
The wind that touched my blushing cheeks
空高く抜けた
Blew through the high sky
いつも見ていた　近いようで遠くて
I was always watching, seemingly close but far
いつだって届かない…
Always out of reach...
どうして？と　問いかけた声も揺れる
I asked, "Why?" and even my voice wavered
ゆらゆら水面に浮かんだ　月は何も
Faintly floating on the water's surface, the moon...
語らないただの傍観者
Doesn't say anything, just a bystander
「同じね」　握る手が痛い
"We're the same," the hand I grip hurts
いたずらに風が吹く朝
A morning where the wind blows mischievously
樹々の葉がじゃれあう声に
To the sound of the leaves of the trees frolicking
合わせて駆け出す君を
Along with you who starts running
日々を
Those days
ただ夢中で追いかけてた
I was just chasing after you frantically
その横顔が見てるのは
What that side profile of yours is looking at
遥か遠くここじゃなくて
Is far, far away, and not here
海が満ち、また引いていく夕凪
The sea rises and ebbs again in the evening calm
心の岸に打ち寄せられた
Washed up on the shore of my heart
決意は明日の光
Is the determination, the light of tomorrow
信じて
Believe...
ねぇ　問いかけた声が響く
Hey, the voice that asked echoes
はらはらと一緒に夜空
Along with the fluttering... the night sky
駆けていけば
If I run...
あの丘に日差しさす頃に
By the time the sun shines on that hill
「見つけた」　願いは宝石
"I found it," my wish is a gemstone
輝き出す
Starting to sparkle
the ebb and flow of my mind…
the ebb and flow…
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you very much!
最後の曲、ebb and flowでした！
That was the last song, ebb and flow!
というわけで皆さん、上着のお披露目です、みんな見てー！
So everyone, this is the jacket reveal, look everyone!
みてみて かわいいでしょう いいでしょう いいでしょう
Look, look! It's cute, isn't it? Good, right? Good, right?
というわけでね、これをね、5期生のみんなにも自慢したいと思うので、呼びたいと思います。
So, I want to show this off to my 5th-gen friends as well, so I'm going to call them over.
自慢されたい5期生のみんなー！
Everyone from the 5th generation who wants to see me show off!
わーい
Yay!
ねぇ、みてみて！
Hey, look, look!
いいでしょう？
Isn't it nice?
いいじゃーん。ちょっと待って、触ってもいい？
It's nice! Wait, can I touch it?
やだやだ！ちょっと待って！ほら！
No, no! Wait! Look!
やめてよー
Stop it!
脱がさないでよ！
Don't take it off!
上着ちょうだいよ、ねね。
Give me your jacket, Nene.
これ？
This?
あ、ないね。
Ah, it's not here.
あれ？なんで？みんな、みんなごめん。
Huh? Why? Everyone, sorry.
上着は、ポルカ、嘘でしょ？
The jacket... Polka, are you kidding me?
これちょうだいよ。やだー！
Give me this! No!
脱がさないで！
Don't take it off!
今日きたばっかなのに。
I just put it on today!
めっちゃかわいい。なんかさ、アップでさ。
It's so cute. Let's see a close-up.
回って、回って。
Spin around, spin around.
桃に桃がある。
There's a peach on the peach.
いいでしょう？かわいいなぁ、ありがとう。
Isn't it nice? It's so cute, thank you.
というわけでですね、ねねからお披露目があったのと一緒に、もう一つ告知があります！
So, along with Nene's reveal, I have one more announcement!
なんだなんだ？
What is it, what is it?
ねねの... お誕生日の... グッズが出ます！
Nene's... birthday... goods are being released!
イェーイ！
Yay!
というわけで、詳細こちら、ドン！
And here are the details, boom!
桃鈴ねね 誕生記念2022 誕生記念グッズが出ます！
Momosuzu Nene Birthday Celebration 2022 Birthday Memorial Goods are coming out!
イェーイ！
Yay!
詳細をね、今から発表していこうと思うんですけど、ちょっとね、もう書いてあるんだけど、一つずつ確認していきたいと思います。
I'm going to announce the details now... well, they're already written there, but I'd like to go through them one by one.
あ、みんなこっちきて。
Ah, everyone come here.
あのね、まず、あの、今回もフルセットがあります。直筆サインあります。
So, first off, we have a full set again this time. It includes a handwritten autograph.
おー！
Oh!
あ、ちょっと、見えちゃう！やだー、映さないでよ！
Ah, wait, it's showing! No, don't film that!
というわけで、一個ずつ見ていきましょう、こちら！
Anyway, let's look at them one by one. Here!
まず、ラバーマットが出ます！
First, a rubber mat is coming out!
ねねのイラストって、なもり先生リスペクトしてるんだけど...
Nene's illustrations respect Namori-sensei...
やめてください！やめてください！
Please stop! Please stop!
なもり先生リスペクトしてるんだけど、今回ね、そのリスペクトしてる大好きな大好きな先生に、お誕生日の記念のラバーマットを書いていただきました！
I respect Namori-sensei, and this time, that teacher I respect and love so much drew the birthday memorial rubber mat for me!
うれしい！
I'm so happy!
ねねがね、お部屋でなんか音楽を、こう、なんか、思い浮かべてる、みたいな感じで。
It's like Nene is in her room, thinking about music or something.
ネッコめっちゃおるじゃん。
There are so many Nekko.
そう、ネッコ、めっちゃネッコにむぎゅってされてるの。
Yeah, Nekko... I'm being squeezed by so many Nekko.
すごいかわいいので、よかったら詳細のページで確認してみて下さい。
It's very cute, so please check it out on the details page.
そして次のグッズ！
And the next item!
次は、ネッコなトートバッグが出ます！
Next, a Nekko tote bag is coming out!
ねぇ、みんなよくみて、よくみて。
Hey, everyone look closely, look closely.
イラスト：桃鈴ねね。というわけでですね、今回ねねが描き下ろしました！
Illustration: Momosuzu Nene. That's right, Nene drew this herself!
描き下ろしっていうか、なんか普通にいつも書いてるやつ...
You say drawn for this, but it's like what you usually draw...
違う！描き下ろし！
No! It's drawn specifically for this!
いつも書いてる... ポルカすごいでしょう、これ。
What you always draw... Polka, isn't this great?
いや、すごいけど...
Well, it's great, but...
困ってるじゃん、やめてあげて。
She's troubled, stop it.
なんか、いい感じだね、このくらいのネッコ。自己主張、あんまり主張しすぎず...
It's nice, this kind of Nekko. It's not too assertive...
そうそうそう、なんか、隠れ、隠れオタクグッズ、みたいな感じでね、使っていただきたいと思います。
Exactly, I want people to use it like a "hidden otaku goods" kind of thing.
ねねの描き下ろしなんで、よろしくお願いします。
It's Nene's own drawing, so please check it out.
そして、そして、次！
And, and, next!
なんだなんだ？
What is it, what is it?
ネッコのパンツが出ます！
Nekko pants are coming out!
イェーイ！...イェーイ、なのかな？
Yay! ...Is it a "yay"?
ねぇ、みてみて、超かわいいでしょう。
Look, look, it's super cute, right?
これさ、ねねがお尻にネッコの顔があるの。
This, there's a Nekko face on the butt.
そうそう、ねねが、ネッコのみんなをめっちゃ敷く！
Yeah, Nene will sit on all the Nekkos!
敷く、尻に敷く。
Sit on them, under the butt.
遠巻きに見てるけど、ポルカ、どうこれ？
You're looking from afar, Polka, what do you think?
いやなんかさ、あれかな、でもなんか、ショーパンみたいな感じだよね。
Well, you know... maybe... but it feels like short pants.
そう、ユニセックスなんだよね。今回ユニセックス、女の子のねっ子も履けるようにユニセックスにいたしまして。
Right, it's unisex. This time it's unisex, so girl Nekkos can wear it too.
なのでね、注意としてはね、こちらのほう開きませんので気をつけてください。
So, as a warning, the front doesn't open, so be careful.
あ、可愛い、へぇー。だからパジャマ代わりに...
Oh, cute. So as pajamas...
そう、パジャマ代わりにもしてください。
Yes, please use them as pajamas too.
そして本当に実際に下着としても身につけて、みんなのお尻の下にはネッコがいるって思ったら面白いので、よろしくお願いします。
And really, wear them as underwear, it's funny to think there's a Nekko under everyone's butt, so please!
ねぽらぼで履きます！お揃いのパンツです！
NePoLaBo will wear them! Matching pants!
記念グッズでパンツ出した人...
Someone who released pants as memorial goods...
すごかった、でも、運営さんからめちゃめちゃ批判を買って...
It was amazing, but I got a lot of criticism from the management...
やめろ、その話はやめろ！後で聞くから！ねんねんお願い！次！
Stop, stop talking about that! I'll hear it later! Nene, please! Next!
はい！
Yes!
そしてフルセットご購入してくれた方には、ねねの描き下ろし直筆サイン入りポストカード！
And for those who purchase the full set, you'll get a postcard with Nene's newly drawn illustration and handwritten signature!
おおー！すごーい！
Ooh! Amazing!
今回はね、しかもね、あの特典のボイスがつくんですけど...
This time, there's even a bonus voice included...
普段ねねのASMRの枠ってちょっとおふざけしちゃうんだけど、ガチマジASMR、録り下ろして来ました！
Usually, Nene's ASMR streams are a bit silly, but I've recorded some serious, real ASMR for this!
おー！すごーい！ガチだ！
Ooh! Amazing! It's the real deal!
そして直筆のサイン入りポストカードではですね、前回、去年の時もお誕生日の時にやったんだけど、サインとちょっとメッセージみたいな感じで書いていけたらいいなと思ってますので、皆さんよろしくお願いします！
And for the handwritten signed postcard, like I did for my birthday last year, I'm thinking of writing a signature and a little message, so please look forward to it, everyone!
お願いします！おー！
Please look forward to it! Ooh!
みんな、どう？ねねの今回のグッズ。
What do you all think of Nene's merchandise this time?
すごーい！いい感じ！
Amazing! It's great!
じゃあパンツ履くでしょ？
So, you'll wear the pants, right?
サインしてくれる？じゃあ、パンツに。
Will you sign them then? The pants.
いいよ、お尻の...あ、ここにする？ここ。
Sure, on the butt... oh, should I do it here? Here.
ちょっと前はな...
A bit in the front is...
何それ？すごーい！
What's that? Amazing!
ラミィも履くでしょ？
Lamy will wear them too, right?
え、ねぽらぼで履くでしょ？
Eh, NePoLaBo will wear them, right?
あ、そう、ねぽらぼで履く。ねぽらぼでお揃いにするので、皆様もお揃いにしてください！
Ah, right, NePoLaBo will wear them. We'll be matching in NePoLaBo, so everyone else, please match with us too!
お揃いにしてください！
Please match with us!
パッカーン！
Pakkan!
開かないでしょ！
It won't open!
開かない。あ、開かない？
It won't open. Oh, it won't open?
ポルカもそれ真似るよ。
Polka will imitate that too.
開かない。開かないから。
It won't open. Because it won't open.
というわけでね、最後にね、上着着たし、みんなで可愛い写真撮って終わりにしたいと思います！
So, finally, since I put on my jacket, I want to end by taking a cute picture with everyone!
わーい！いいね！
Yay! That's good!
みんな準備いいですか？あ、みんな来て来て、固まって固まって。
Is everyone ready? Ah, everyone come here, huddle up, huddle up.
あ、アップ、アップで可愛く撮ってください！アップ、アップ！
Ah, up close, take a cute photo up close! Up close, up close!
イエーイ！
Yay!
みんな、ありがとう！というわけで、今日のねねの配信はここまで！
Thank you, everyone! So, that's it for Nene's stream today!
皆さん、たくさん見てくれてありがとう！
Thank you everyone for watching so much!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
四人とも、ありがとう！あ、四人じゃない、三人もありがとう！
Thank you to all four of us! Ah, not four, thank you to the three of you too!
おめでとうー！
Congratulations!
バイバーイ！おめでとう！またね！おつねねー！ハッピーバースデー！
Bye-bye! Congratulations! See you! Otsu-Nene! Happy Birthday!
フルセット購入特典
なもり描き下ろしポストカード
誕生日記念フルセット
直筆サイン入りポストカード + 特典ASMRボイス
Full Set Purchase Bonus
Postcard Drawn by Namori
Birthday Commemorative Full Set
Handwritten Signed Postcard + Bonus ASMR Voice
誕生日記念フルセット
ラバーマット
Nekko トートバッグ
Nekko ボクサーパンツ
ASMR 記念ボイス 1種
Birthday Commemorative Full Set
Rubber Mat
Nekko Tote Bag
Nekko Boxer Pants
1 Type of ASMR Commemorative Voice
お披露目あり！
3/2 21:00 START
桃鈴ねね 2nd Birthday 3Dライブ
Reveal Included!
3/2 21:00 START
Momosuzu Nene 2nd Birthday 3D Live